# Mr, Isaac Kelechi

# Full Stack Developer

kcib.mail@gmail.com • 234 701 650 5681 • linkedin.com/in/kcib • kcib.netlify.app

#### **Profile**

Full Stack Developer with 5+ years of experience from creating, designing and managing web & mobile applications. Proficient with developing database, creating user interfaces, writing and testing code, debugging issues, implementing new features based on user feedback and collaborating with any teams to develop a product.

## **Professional Experience**

Jun 2021 – present Port Harcourt, Nigeria

# Full Stack Developer, Quelib

- Created and implemented a full working mobile application from scratch to production with both back-end and front-end
- Marketed and Advertised the app via Facebook and Twitter and getting over 200% increase in users
- Push app to Google play store

Nov 2021 – Mar 2022 Ikeja Lagos, Nigeria

### Mobile App Developer, FoodNow

- Identify, analyzed and debugged app issues with both back-end and front-end developers on the team.
- Recreated, Designed & maintained the app.
- Added a payment wallet, social system & Organizations

Nov 2020 – May 2021 Port Harcourt, Nigeria

## Full Stack Developer, Ohms

- Created the wireframe and designed the app using flutter framework
- Developed the backend using php mysql and connected to the frontend using restful api

Oct 2019 – Nov 2020 Port Harcourt, Nigeria

#### Full Stack Developer, Albaama

- Used HTML CSS to create an ecommerce website with stunning UI and great User experience
- Completely created am admin section with full functional using php mysql

#### **Skills** HTML CSS (Tailwind CSS, Styled-Component) JavaScript (JQuery) React.js (TypeScript & Next.js) Flutter/Dart PHP Node.js (Express.js, Sequelize) MySql Firebase Git & Github Adobe illustrator MongoDB Figma GraphQl & Rest Api Blockchain Heroku & Netlify Solidity

#### **Education**

Sep 2017 Bauchi, Nigeria **Abubakar Tafewa Belewa University, Computer Science**